export const allQuestions = [
    // Questions to ask 

{
    prompt: "Who designed the national emblem of Bangladesh?",
    a: "Zainul Abedin",
    b: "SM Sultan",
    c: "Quamrul Hassan",
    d: "Murtoza Bashir",
    solution: "c",
},
{

    prompt: "The Constitution Day of Bangladesh?",
    a: "16th December",
    b: "23rd October",
    c: "7th March",
    d: "4th November",
    solution: "d",
},
{

    prompt: "Which is the southern most district in Bangladesh?",
    a: "Chittagong",
    b: "Bhola",
    c: "Cox's Bazar",
    d: "Patuakhali",
    solution: "c",
},
{

    prompt: "Where is the monument 'Sangshaptak' situated?",
    a: "At Jahangirnagar University",
    b: "At University of Dhaka",
    c: "At Khulna University",
    d: "At Rajshahi University",
    solution: "a",
},
{

    prompt: "Bir Srestho Ruhul Amin was?",
    a: "Flight Lieutenant",
    b: "Squadron Engineer",
    c: "Lance Naik",
    d: "Captain",
    solution: "b",
},
{

    prompt: "The Architect of Shaheed Minar is?",
    a: "Hamidur Rahman",
    b: "Shamim Shikder",
    c: "Aminul Islam",
    d: "Nitun Kundu",
    solution: "a",
},
{

    prompt: "Sundarban was declard a 'World Heritage' by?",
    a: "UNESCO",
    b: "UNICEF",
    c: "UNDP",
    d: "UNHCR",
    solution: "a",
},
{

    prompt: "Which is the widest river of Bangladesh?",
    a: "The Padma",
    b: "The Meghna",
    c: "The Jamuna",
    d: "The Surma",
    solution: "b",
},
{

    prompt: "Which is the largest riverine delta in the world?",
    a: "Bangladesh",
    b: "Egypt",
    c: "Bhutan",
    d: "Laos",
    solution: "a",
},
{

    prompt: "Which is the largest district of Bangladesh?",
    a: "Dhaka",
    b: "Chittagong",
    c: "Rangamati",
    d: "Dinajpur",
    solution: "c",
},
];